{
    "id": "0d56153f3a124f9aab804ca8bfe7e674",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I told him why I ............................... that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "did",
                "will do"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the boys whether they .................................... the problems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "solved",
                "have solved",
                "had solved"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will go home during the vacation so that I ...................................... my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can see",
                "could see",
                "might see"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Although they ......................................, they did not lose heart.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "defeated",
                "had defeated",
                "were defeated"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Our teacher taught us that virtue ...................................... its own reward.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Our holy books tell us that man .................................. mortal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "will be"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Just as I entered the room, the bell ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ring",
                "rang",
                "rung"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will break your neck if you ...................................... that again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "did",
                "had done"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house where James ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives",
                "is living"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He declared that he will not believe it even if he ....................................... it with his own eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sees",
                "saw",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}